=Let's Go Fighting= =Episode 17=
= لنبدأ القتال = = الحلقة 17 =
Is this the surprise you gave me?
هل هذه هي المفاجأة التي أعطيتني إياها؟
No.
رقم.
This is the breakfast for you.
هذا هو الفطور لك.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
I'm here to help Xiao Li carry her luggage.
أنا هنا لمساعدة Xiao Li في حمل أمتعتها.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
It's inappropriate
انه غير مناسب
for you two to live together.
لكي تعيشما معًا.
It's not that.
انها ليست التي.
Before,
قبل،
I lived here as my sister
عشت هنا كأختي
to investigate the truth.
للتحقيق في الحقيقة.
Since the matter is settled,
منذ أن تمت تسوية الأمر ،
it's not suitable for me to live here
ليس من المناسب لي العيش هنا
and I can move out.
ويمكنني الخروج.
I don't mind.
أنا لا أمانع.
Don't move out.
لا تخرج.
I bought four tickets for outdoor camping.
اشتريت أربع تذاكر للتخييم في الهواء الطلق.
Let's go and relax together!
دعنا نذهب ونسترخي معا!
Xue,
Xue ،
I...
أنا...
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
Don't like this kind of activity
لا تحب هذا النوع من النشاط
after being rich?
بعد الثراء؟
Dear me,
عزيزي
that's not what I meant.
هذا ليس ما قصدته.
Oh.
أوه.
Li,
لي ،
you still owe me a reward.
ما زلت تدين لي بمكافأة.
Li.
لي.
Don't you like Mo Chen?
ألا تحب مو تشن؟
Why do you move away?
لماذا تبتعد؟
I used to live with him
كنت أعيش معه
as my sister.
أختي.
But now he knows my identity.
لكنه الآن يعرف هويتي.
I feel a little uncomfortable.
أشعر بقليل من عدم الارتياح.
But isn't it better to
لكن أليس من الأفضل أن
clear the air?
تنقية الهواء؟
Unlike me and Lu Xingjie.
خلافا لي ولو Xingjie.
Hey,
يا،
Do you give up?
هل تستسلم؟
Lu,
لو ،
what the hell is going on with you?
ما الذي يجري معك بحق الجحيم؟
Why did you hide Xia Xingrun's affairs
لماذا أخفيت شؤون شيا شينغرن
from me?
مني؟
It was too urgent at the time.
كانت ملحة للغاية في ذلك الوقت.
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
In fact, from that day on,
في الواقع ، من ذلك اليوم فصاعدًا ،
I knew
كنت أعلم
Li only had eyes for you.
كان لي عيون لك فقط.
Lu...
لو ...
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
It is me who was heartless
أنا الذي كان بلا قلب
and blind.
وأعمى.
Ah?
آه؟
One more time.
مرة أخرى.
OK.
نعم.
Come on.
هيا.
I think
أظن
he's avoiding me on purpose.
إنه يتجنبني عن قصد.
Then you should take the initiative.
إذن عليك أن تأخذ زمام المبادرة.
Look at me.
انظر إليَّ.
Let me try.
دعني اجرب.
So impressive!
مؤثرة جدا!
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Let's go cycling.
لنذهب لركوب الدراجات.
Go.
يذهب.
Come on!
هيا!
They are catching up!
إنهم يلحقون بالركب!
Go!
يذهب!
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
You don't make an effort!
أنت لا تبذل جهدا!
How can we win them?
كيف يمكننا الفوز بهم؟
I'm tired
أنا مجهد
and don't want to ride anymore.
ولا تريد الركوب بعد الآن.
Let's go and see.
دعونا نذهب ونرى.
I didn't say anything.
لم أقل شيئًا.
Why are you angry?
لماذا انت غاضب؟
Let me try.
دعني اجرب.
Lu,
لو ،
what's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
Lu,
لو ،
it was Xue
كان شيويه
who took care of you.
من اعتنى بك.
You were so drunk
كنت في حالة سكر جدا
that you were almost beaten to death on the roadside.
أنك تعرضت للضرب حتى الموت على جانب الطريق.
It was she
كانت هي
who took care of you every day.
من اعتنى بك كل يوم.
I vaguely guessed it.
خمنت ذلك بشكل غامض.
Then why are you avoiding her?
إذن لماذا تتجنبها؟
That's why
لهذا
I don't know how to face her.
لا أعرف كيف أواجهها.
You have to know what you want.
عليك أن تعرف ما تريد.
Once you miss some people,
بمجرد أن تفتقد بعض الأشخاص ،
you may not be able to get them back.
قد لا تتمكن من استعادتها.
The process is very tortuous,
العملية شاقة للغاية ،
but I think
لكنني أعتقد
it is the best start now.
إنها أفضل بداية الآن.
Li,
لي ،
thank you.
شكرا لك.
I bought water.
اشتريت الماء.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Let's get back on the bike.
دعنا نعود إلى الدراجة.
Bye!
وداعا!
Let's go.
لنذهب.
I'll take you somewhere.
سآخذك إلى مكان ما.
Where?
أين؟
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Why haven't we arrived yet?
لماذا لم نصل بعد؟
OK, stop.
نعم توقف.
Yoo-Hoo!
يو-هوو!
=Let's Go Fighting=
= لنبدأ القتال =
♪The soul falls to the bottom of the lake♪
الروح تسقط في قاع البحيرة
♪Broken stars pierce the sky♪
♪ النجوم المكسورة تخترق السماء ♪
♪Secrets hidden in the cloud♪
♪ أسرار مخبأة في السحابة ♪
♪From the Milky Way♪
♪ من درب التبانة ♪
♪Belong to you♪
ملك لك ♪